Want to know who killed your father?
Don't go. Uncle Punlop will kill you.
I was just thinking about you,
my dear niece.
Rin!
Help me.
Who did this to you?!
Who's your boss, Uncle?
Why ask about Damon out of the blue?
‪-Dad!
‪-Hey!
Pok, help me! Please help my son.
Where are my brothers?
Where the hell are my brothers?!
What are you doing in here?
Answer me!
- Quick, we need to split up.
- Let's go.
- Found anything?
- Not yet.
Your sister's really good
at her job, my dear Te.
She's so many times better than you.
Everybody's praising her.
You can take a long rest.
Or if you want to be with your dad,
I can send you there too.
Hey!
I'll check it out first.
Okay. I'll keep a lookout.
Dhammatat, is it this one?
It needs a password.
Just bring it back.
Okay.
- Aru, quick!
- I got it.
What is it,
Mr. Former CEO of 3C?
Free Rin and bring her to me.
To you?
Why?
You're a vegetable.
You don't need that many bodyguards.
She's one of my people.
One of your people?
Yet you let her be
with an enemy like Taiga?
Do you know how damaging that is?
You've run out of chances, Naruban.
She isn't one of your people.
If you want her,
there's only one way.
Trade Taiga with her.
You can open it, right?
We must be careful.
All the files are encrypted.
Wherever we open it, they can trace it.
So what do we do?
We already got it,
yet it's so hard to open.
Let me think.
It must have a list of names
and all the files about Fire Phoenix.
We'll use it as leverage in exchange
for the antidotes and vaccines
and as evidence to take them down.
What?
What the heck? You're supposed to be
the best hacker in the universe!
We can't be rash.
Give it to me. I'll find a way to open it.
One day.
Give me just one day.
I promise I can open it tomorrow.
Ms. Nun.
Mr. Taiga.
Someone attacked me.
Who?
Ms. Atinuch came in for some documents
and found you lying there.
I was passing by,
so she asked me to stay with you.
The doctor's on his way here.
I'm alright.
The security cameras.
3C-Coin got tanked?
Calm down, Ms. Nun.
Check the security cameras.
Find out who broke in here.
What are you doing in here?
There were two of them.
They broke in here and attacked me.
You're okay.
I'll be right by your side.
Please don't be afraid.
How come 3C-Coin got tanked?
Mom?
Why'd you do this to me?
You said 3C-Coin would get us rich.
How come everyone's dumping it?
How did its price
drop to only a few dollars?!
Mom,
please give me the antidote.
Are you trying to kill me?
I'm your son!
Are you demanding my gratitude
just because you're my mom
who bore and raised me?
But isn't that just your duty as a wife?
A wife my dad doesn't love
and doesn't want to be with.
He never even intended
to make you his wife.
This woman your dad doesn't love
and doesn't want to be with,
who he never intended to make as his wife…
From now on,
she's all I'll ever be,
just like you said.
Your dad supports you
in everything you do.
But your sister,
it's as if she doesn't have a dad.
She's had to struggle to prove herself.
Because Nun's not his daughter?
Yes!
But so what?
Does that give you the right
to insult her
and bully her anyway you want?
Mom…
Think of it as giving
your sister a chance.
Let her take 3C to another level.
And as for you,
you can just lie down and wait here
until I give you the antidote.
Don't worry,
I won't let you and your dad die.
Everyone will be jealous
of our oh-so-perfect family.
Just let me and your sister
become the leaders.
Trust me, honey.
The footage is gone,
right when they broke in.
That means
they can hack our system.
I'll have the whole system replaced.
Good idea, Ms. Nun.
I'm going to make 3C even more successful.
Mr. Taiga,
please root for me.
We still can't open up the files.
Dhammatat said
it should be done by tomorrow.
How's everything on your end, Sun?
My team's working on a code
to compromise their system.
We're creating fake news
to trick investors,
and we're pumping out
traps and teams of IOs.
We're trying every way
to tank 3C-Coin's price as hard as we can.
It'll work, right?
Of course.
Good crypto traders can tell
that losses are normal,
but if they occur frequently,
then something's off.
Soon,
a 3C-coin will be worth only a rock.
Trust me, Aru,
when something seems too good to be true,
you have to be careful.
You stay safe too, Sun.
I'm worried about you.
Share me some of your pain
so you can smile.
I want to find Rin.
Do you love her?
I'm worried about her.
She's sick.
Whoever you're worried about,
I'll worry about them too.
But if you ask me how I feel,
I'll have to be honest…
Love
isn't something you can share.
I'm not so generous that I'd feel nothing.
It's just that I'm accepting it
and waiting patiently
for the day you'll be mine
and mine alone forever.
Can you open it yet, Dhammatat?
Dhammatat?
Dhammatat!
Mr. Khanin!
Mr. Khanin?
Wake up, Mr. Khanin!
Please wake up.
Damn you, Dhammatat!
Where'd he go?
He's not in this house either.
He ran away.
Ran away?
To where?
Still, that doesn't matter
as much as Mr. Naruban's flash drive.
He has it.
You shouldn't leave the house
until you can open the flash drive
and take out all the files
from Fire Phoenix.
I'll open it somewhere else,
- so they can't trace this place.
- It's fine if they do.
But the flash drive needs to be here,
and all the files must be opened first.
Who do you work for?
You're not just some hacker, are you?
And I take it you're not just
a police officer who got framed
and used to work for Fire Phoenix.
That's a really deep background check.
You must have
a lot of skill and connections.
The flash drive isn't here.
So Dhammatat fooled us?
I'm going to see Taiga.
He and Rin aren't safe now.
I'll come too.
You won't be able to help me
even if you go.
But we're a team!
You should just stay here.
Find out about Dhammatat.
Tell Sun to help find him
as soon as possible.
Ms. Ratee!
PERMANENTLY CLOSED!!!
I can't find Dhammatat at all.
Mr. Naruban's flash drive is gone too.
Who knows what information
he's got already.
Relax, Aru.
I'll help you find it.
I'm sorry, Sun.
You're already busy enough
with the 3C-Coin thing,
since you got its price so low.
No worries.
Turning fake news into real news
isn't hard to do.
With investments, knowledge does matter,
but keeping a level head matters the most.
People who aren't level-headed
tend to believe it when they hear,
"An insider told me this."
Then, they're trapped by their own greed,
and the fake news
will drive the coin's price down
even further.
We need to make 3C pay, no matter what.
We need to find Rin.
I never expected
that Dhammatat would betray us!
Till now, we still can't find him.
Taiga,
Dhammatat knows everything
about you and Rin.
You have to be careful
because now, everyone around you
is a member of Fire Phoenix.
And so are you, right?
Yes.
I used to be in Fire Phoenix.
I used to throw people
who stood in their way in jail.
Until one day,
I was betrayed by my boss,
whom I trusted and believed in the most.
I was the scapegoat
for a crime I didn't commit.
So I asked myself,
"What did I do all that for?"
As an honorable policeman,
I shouldn't have to serve those outlaws.
So I decided to walk away.
But then…
my family got murdered.
Just like your family did.
I'll never forgive Fire Phoenix.
I'll go after Damon
for ordering everyone's murder.
What took you so long,
Lieutenant Dhammatat?
What did you get?
It was in Naruban's office, Boss.
What's in it?
I still can't open it.
It’s heavily encrypted.
Even a pro like you can't do it?
I'm sorry.
I tried.
‪But…
If you give me more time, I will--
Take out all the files.
Okay, Boss.
Boss?
Once I can access the files…
can I stop going undercover?
You work in secret,
yet you want to back out?
You really think your victims
will let you off easy?
I want to live a normal life, Boss.
I want to quit.
You're very skilled.
I chose you for such an important job
because you don't seem like a cop.
You went undercover for years
until Taiga trusted you.
That must've been so hard.
So?
Do you see those people
as your true friends now?
I don't want to fool anyone anymore, Boss.
Friendship is good.
But the world's justice matters more.
We can't choose how we die,
but we can choose how we live.
How do you want people to remember you?
An ordinary man, Boss.
Okay.
Maybe you're feeling pressured today.
But let me warn you.
Whenever you reveal your identity,
those who you believe are your friends
will be ready to trample on you
and despise you.
They'll never welcome you again.
Until then,
what you should do
is uphold what's right.
Fire Phoenix will make the world better.
And for every change,
those who sacrificed
will be remembered and praised.
If you want the world
to stay the same,
then go back to them.
Go back to that life
where all you can be…
is some silly hacker.
I can still trust you, right?
Hey, how'd you follow me here?
In your backpack.
A tracker? When did you put it in here?
I put it there to track Taiga.
I didn't think it'd be helpful one day
for finding a backstabbing friend.
Fire Phoenix' files aren't in here.
I used a replica to fool my boss.
Come on. Let's go somewhere else first.
You can open it, right?
We must be careful.
All the files are encrypted.
Wherever we open it, they can trace it.
The flash drive in your office
has been stolen.
The flash drive
holds the password that can be used
to access every member's info.
But what matters more than the info
is the mask.
Fire Phoenix' mask.
You need it for meetings.
No one reveals their identity.
Find a way to get into my home
and take it.
There's only one week left
before Fire Phoenix has a big meeting.
BABY, CATCH ME IF YOU CAN
Hey, stop right there!
I'm sure Punlop
will attend Fire Phoenix' meeting.
You have to be careful, Taiga,
because if he recognizes you,
you'll be in danger,
even if you're behind the mask.
I don't think it's just the mask
that allows us to go in there.
If Dhammatat were still with us,
everything would be easier.
Dhammatat's a part of Fire Phoenix too.
I don't think so.
I had my friends who are ex-cops
look into him.
He's not a part of them.
He's just one of Punlop's henchmen.
I overlooked it.
I never doubted
why Dhammatat knew far too much,
far too much for an ordinary hacker.
Just because of friendship,
we let our guard down.
Taiga,
if this time,
you're going to the core of Fire Phoenix
to destroy it from the inside,
we need to take the passcode,
the meeting location,
and the updated information from Naruban.
Punlop.
A reward for a man who's no longer needed.
Rest in peace.
Die a slow death.
Or if you can't take it…
just let your heart stop beating.
A lousy husband like you
shouldn't get to live
and torture Mrs. Giranun.
Let's welcome our new shareholder.
He's a famous media mogul in the US
who's eager to invest with 3C Group
to build a new future
for Thailand.
Mr. Robert told us
that he's sent his representative
named
Ms. Rateerungsri Clay.
Good afternoon, everyone.
What can 3C-Coin even do
other than tank more and more every day?
When it profited us,
you never got involved.
Okay.
From now on, we need to work together.
I have the right to speak, give orders,
and veto everything.
- If you're here to pick a fight--
- Stop it, Ms. Nun.
Remember why I'm here.
I'm a shareholder.
Please use your brain
more than your emotions.
I'll forget everything that's happened
to let you redeem yourself.
Let's work together,
so that 3C-Coin's value
will profit us both.
Does that sound good, Ms. Ratee?
The router's dead.
We'll give you a replacement.
I happened to bring one.
- I'll go grab it.
- Huh?
What's up?
No, thanks!
I'm not buying a lotto this time.
I don't care if there's a lucky number
or a guru!
Wait.
You're looking for this, right?
How's my dad doing?
Not very well.
He's still alive, right?
Yes.
My dad once told me
he's keeping something very important.
I did some searching and found this.
It's not something unimportant
that anyone can have.
Hurry up and go.
I disabled the alarm, but it won't be long
before it goes off.
Are you okay?
Go, now!
Go!
We should thank your husband
for always working so hard.
The virus from 3C
is about to conquer the world.
The virus,
the vaccine,
and the cure
can only be bought with 3C-coins.
He and his son never told me much at all.
My life's like a flower,
beautiful,
but worth nothing to them.
Thank you so much, Punlop.
You're the only one who sees my worth.
I know you're not just a fragrant flower.
You're beautiful,
precious,
and smart.
You make people fall in love with you
so much, they'd give you their lives.
Taiga.
Naruban's in a coma.
He can't attend the meeting.
The passcode will be erased.
If you use his mask to attend it,
you'll get caught for sure.
Mr. Punlop will be working with us.
- To do what?
- Executive secretary to the CEO.
Wait, how come
you didn't get the email like we did?
I don't have a lot of time left.
The side effects of the antidote
has changed my body.
The symptoms are similar to…
Cancer?!
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya